[
  {
    "question": "1. ะะปั ะฝะฐัะฐะปะฐ ะบะฒะตััะฐ ัะตะฑะต ะฝัะถะฝะพ ะฝะฐัะพะดะธัััั ะฝะฐ ะงะธัััั ะฟััะดะฐั. ะะฐะบ ะฑัะดะตัั ะฝะฐ ะผะตััะต ะฟะธัะธ \"ั ััั\".",
    "answer": ["ะฏ ััั"],
    "hint": "ะงะธัััะต ะฟััะดั",
    "progress_bar": "๐---๐--๐--๐---๐--๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [0%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "2. ยซะกะปัะถะธัั ะฑั ัะฐะด โ ะฟัะธัะปัะถะธะฒะฐัััั ัะพัะฝะพยป\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะฐะนะดะธ ะฟะฐะผััะฝะธะบ ะัะธะฑะพะตะดะพะฒั ะธ ัะฐััะผะพััะธ ะตะณะพ\n\n๐ ะกะบะพะปัะบะพ ัะตะปะพะฒะตะบ ะฟัะธัััััะฒัะตั ะฝะฐ ะฟะฐะผััะฝะธะบะต ะัะธะฑะพะตะดะพะฒั?",
    "answer": ["13"],
    "hint": "ะงะธััะพะฟััะดะฝัะน ะฑัะป., ะฝะฐะฟัะพัะธะฒ ะดะพะผะฐ โ14",
    "progress_bar": "๐ถโโ๏ธ---๐--๐--๐---๐--๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [0%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "3. ะัะพะณัะปัะนัั ะฟะพ ะงะธัััะผ ะฟััะดะฐะผ. ะะพะณะดะฐ ะดะพะนะดะตัั ะดะพ ะบะพะฝัะฐ, ะดะตัะถะธัั ะฟัะฐะฒะตะต. ะะพะฟัะพะฑัะน ะฑะตะท ะฝะฐะฒะธะณะฐัะพัะฐ ะฝะฐะนัะธ ะทะดะฐะฝะธะต ะฟะพ ะฐะดัะตัั ะะพะบัะพะฒะบะฐ, 15/16\n\n๐ ะะฐะบะพะน ัะฒะตั ั ะทะดะฐะฝะธั ะฟะพ ะฐะดัะตัั ะะพะบัะพะฒะบะฐ, 15/16?",
    "answer": ["ะทะตะปัะฝัะน", "ะทะตะปะตะฝัะน"],
    "hint": "ัะป. ะะพะบัะพะฒะบะฐ, 15/16 (ัะปะตะดัััะตะต ะทะดะฐะฝะธะต ะฟะพัะปะต ะทะฒะตัะตะน)",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐ถโโ๏ธ--๐--๐---๐---๐---๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [3%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "4. ๐ถโโ๏ธ ะขะตะฟะตัั ะธะดะตะผ ะฟะพ ัะป. ะะพะบัะพะฒะบะฐ ะฒ ััะพัะพะฝั ัะผะตะฝััะตะฝะธั ะฝะพะผะตัะพะฒ. ะะบะพะปะพ ะพััะฐะฝะพะฒะบะธ \"ะัะผัะฝัะบะธะน ะฟะตั.\" ะฝะฐัะพะดะธััั ะฟะพัะพะปัััะฒะพ ะฝะตะบะพะน ัััะฐะฝั\n\n๐ ะะฐะบะพะณะพ ัะฒะตัะฐ ะฝะตั ะฝะฐ ัะปะฐะณะต ััะพะน ัััะฐะฝั? โค ๐ ๐",
    "answer": ["ะถัะปััะน", "ะถะตะปััะน", "๐"],
    "hint": "ัะป. ะะฐัะพัะตะนะบะฐ, 17/6ั1",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐ถโโ๏ธ--๐---๐---๐---๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [14%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "5. ะะดะตะผ ะฒ ะฑะธะฑะปะธะพัะตะบั!\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะ ะกัะฐัะพัะฐะดัะบะพะผ ะฟะตัะตัะปะบะต ะฝะฐะนะดะธ ะะพััะดะฐัััะฒะตะฝะฝัั ะฟัะฑะปะธัะฝัั ะฑะธะฑะปะธะพัะตะบั\n\n๐ ะ ะบะฐะบะพะผ ะฒัะตัะพัะธะนัะบะพะผ ััะตะทะดะต ะธะดะตั ัะตัั ะฝะฐ ะธััะพัะธัะตัะบะพะน ัะฐะฑะปะธัะบะต ะฝะฐ ะทะดะฐะฝะธะธ ะฑะธะฑะปะธะพัะตะบะธ?",
    "answer": ["3", "3ะน", "3-ะน", "ััะตัะธะน"],
    "hint": "ะกัะฐัะพัะฐะดัะบะธะน ะฟะตัะตัะปะพะบ, 9ั1",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐ถโโ๏ธ---๐---๐---๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [23%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "6. ะะดะตะผ... ัะพัะฝะตะต ะธะดะตะผ ะดะฐะปััะต\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะกะฒะตัะฝะธ ะฝะฐ ัะปะธัั ะะฐะฑะตะปะธะฝะฐ. ะะฐะนะดะธ ะทะฐะฒะตะดะตะฝะธะต The black swan\n\n๐ ะะฐะบ ะฝะฐะทัะฒะฐะตััั ะฝะตะฒะธะฝะฝัะน ะฑะฐั ัะฟัะฐะฒะฐ ะพั ะฝะตะณะพ?",
    "answer": ["Bambule"],
    "hint": "ัะป. ะกะพะปัะฝะบะฐ, 1/2",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐ถโโ๏ธ---๐---๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [26%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "7. ะกะตะนัะฐั ะฝะฐะดะพ ะฑััั ะฒะฝะธะผะฐัะตะปัะฝะตะต! ๐ง ะขั ัะผะฝะฐั, ัะฐะบ ััะพ ัะฟัะฐะฒะธัััั))\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะดะตะผ ะฟะพ ัะปะธัะต ะกะพะปัะฝะบะฐ ะฒ ััะพัะพะฝั ะผะพััะฐ. ะะพ ะปะตะฒะพะน ััะพัะพะฝะต, ะฝะต ะดะพัะพะดั ะดะพ ะผะพััะฐ, ะฝะฐะนะดะธ ัััะฑะพะปัะฝัะน ะฑะฐะฝะบ\n\n๐ ะัะฟัะฐะฒั ะผะฝะต ะฝะฐะทะฒะฐะฝะธะต ะณะพัะพะดะฐ",
    "answer": ["ะกะฐะฝะบั-ะะตัะตัะฑััะณ", "ะะธัะตั", "ะกะะ", "ะะตัะตัะฑััะณ"],
    "hint": "ัะป. ะกะพะปัะฝะบะฐ, 13/3ั1",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐ถโโ๏ธ---๐----๐----๐----๐---๐ [32%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "8. ะกัะฐะปะธะฝัะบะฐั ะฒััะพัะบะฐ\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะดะตะผ ะฝะฐ ะะพัะตะปัะฝะธัะตัะบัั ะฝะฐะฑะตัะตะถะฝัั ะบ ััะฐะปะธะฝัะบะพะน ะฒััะพัะบะต\n\n๐ค ะะฝัะตัะตัะฝัะต ัะฐะบัั:\n- ััะพ ะถะธะปะพะต ะทะดะฐะฝะธะต\n- ัะตะฝััะฐะปัะฝัะน ะฒััะพัะฝัะน ะบะพัะฟัั ะฝะฐััะธััะฒะฐะตั 32 ััะฐะถะฐ\n- ะฒััะพัะฐ ะฒะผะตััะต ัะพ ัะฟะธะปะตะผ ัะพััะฐะฒะปัะตั 176 ะผ\n- ะฟะพ ะฑะพะบะฐะผ ัะฐัะฟะพะปะฐะณะฐัััั ะฐัะบะธ ั ะฑะฐัะตะปัะตัะฐะผะธ ะธ ัะบัะปัะฟัััะฐะผะธ ะดะฒัั ัะฐะฑะพัะธั\n\n๐ ะัะพ ะธะทะพะฑัะฐะถะตะฝ ะฝะฐ ัะบัะปัะฟัััะฐั: ะผัะถัะธะฝั, ะถะตะฝัะธะฝั ะธะปะธ ะพะฑะฐ?",
    "answer": ["ะะฑะฐ"],
    "hint": "ะะพัะตะปัะฝะธัะตัะบะฐั ะฝะฐะฑ., 1/15",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐๏ธ---๐ถโโ๏ธ----๐----๐----๐---๐ [40%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "9. ะะทะฑัะบะฐ\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะต ะดะพัะพะดั ะดะพ ะฟะฐัะบะฐ ะะฐััะดัะต, ะฟะพะฒะตัะฝะธ ะฝะฐะฟัะฐะฒะพ ะฝะฐ ะะธัะฐะนะณะพัะพะดัะบะธะน ะฟัะพะตะทะด. ะ ะะปัะธะฝัะบะพะผ ัะบะฒะตัะต ัะฐัะฟะพะปะพะถะตะฝ ะฟะฐะผััะฝะธะบ ะะธัะธะปะปั ะธ ะะตัะพะดะธั. ะะฝะธะผะฐัะตะปัะฝะพ ัะฐััะผะพััะธ ะตะณะพ\n\n๐ ะะฐ ะทะฐะดะฝะตะน ัะฐััะธ ะฟะฐะผััะฝะธะบะฐ ะตััั ััะธ ัะฐะฑะปะธัะบะธ. ะะฐะบะพะต ัะปะพะฒะพ ะฒัะดะตะปะตะฝะพ ะฝะฐ ะฟัะฐะฒะพะน ัะฐะฑะปะธัะบะต?",
    "answer": ["ะฑะฐะฝะบ"],
    "hint": "ะขะฒะตััะบะพะน",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐๏ธ---๐ข----๐ถโโ๏ธ----๐----๐---๐ [47%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "10. ะั ะฝะฐ ัะธะฝะธัะฝะพะน ะฟััะผะพะน! (ะฝั ะฝะต ัะพะฒัะตะผ ะฟััะผะพะน, ะธ ะฝะต ัะพะฒัะตะผ ัะธะฝะธัะฝะพะน)\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะดะตะผ ััะดะฐ, ะณะดะต ะฑัะป ัะฝัั ะปะตะณะตะฝะดะฐัะฝัะน ะฒะธะดะตะพะผะฐัะตัะธะฐะป: https://youtu.be/VvOqC_2-hjw?si=kJYF4ZsW02pDYILt\n\n๐ ะัะดะฐ ะธะดะตะผ?",
    "answer": ["ะัะฐัะฝะฐั ะฟะปะพัะฐะดั"],
    "hint": "ะกะผะพััะธ ะฒะธะดะพั",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐๏ธ---๐ข----๐ฟ----๐ถโโ๏ธ----๐---๐ [66%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "11. ะัะัะะฐะฏ ะฟะะพะฉะฐะั\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะฐ-ะดะฐ, ัะพะฟะฐะตะผ ะฝะฐ ะัะฐัะฝัั ะฟะปะพัะฐะดั. ะะพะณะดะฐ ะฑัะดะตัั ะฝะฐ ะผะตััะต, ะฟะพะดะพะนะดะธ ะบ ะะฐะฒะทะพะปะตั\n\n๐ค ะะฝัะตัะตัะฝัะต ัะฐะบัั:\n- ะะพัะบะพะฒัะบะพะผั ะัะตะผะปั โ ะฑะพะปะตะต 500 ะปะตั\n- ะะฃะั โ ะฑะพะปะตะต 130 ะปะตั\n- ะะฐะฒะทะพะปะตั โ ัะพะฒะฝะพ 100 ะปะตั\n\n๐ ะกะบะพะปัะบะพ ะตะปะตะน ะฟะพัะฐะถะตะฝะพ ั ะะฐะฒะทะพะปะตั?",
    "answer": ["10"],
    "hint": "ะัะฐัะฝะฐั ะฟะปะพัะฐะดั, ะะฐะฒะทะพะปะตะน",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐๏ธ---๐ข----๐ฟ----๐ถโโ๏ธ----๐---๐ [66%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "12. ะัะดะฐ ะธะดะตะผ ะผั ั ะััะฐัะบะพะผ? ะ ััะพััะฑะปะตะฒะพะน ะบัะฟััะต!\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะดะตะผ ะบ ะทะดะฐะฝะธั ัะพ ััะพััะฑะปะตะฒะพะน ะบัะฟััั. ะกะผะพััะธะผ ะฝะฐ ะฟะฐะผััะฝะธะบ ะฝะฐ ะฟัะพัะธะฒะพะฟะพะปะพะถะฝะพะน ััะพัะพะฝะต ัะปะธัั. ะ ัะตััั ะะะะ ะฟะพััะฐะฒะปะตะฝ ะฟะฐะผััะฝะธะบ ะฝะฐะฟัะพัะธะฒ?\n\n๐ ะ ะพัะฒะตัะต ะฝะฐะฟะธัะธ ะณะพัะพะด-ะผะธะปะปะธะพะฝะฝะธะบ, ะฒ ะบะพัะพัะพะผ ะตััั ะฟะปะพัะฐะดั ะธะผะตะฝะธ ะะะ",
    "answer": ["ะะพะฒะพัะธะฑะธััะบ", "ะะพะฒะพัะธะฑ", "ะะกะ"],
    "hint": "ะะพะปััะพะน ัะตะฐัั",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐๏ธ---๐ข----๐ฟ----๐ฐ----๐ถโโ๏ธ---๐ [81%]"
  },
  {
    "question": "13. ะัะฐะฒะธะปัะฝะพ ะฟะพะฝะธะผะฐั, ััะพ ะตัะต ะฝะต ะฑัะป ััะตะดะตะฝ ะฝะธ ะพะดะธะฝ ัะธะฝะฐะฑะพะฝ? ๐ญ\n\n๐ถโโ๏ธ ะะต ะดะตะปะพ! ะะตะณะพะผ ะธะดะตะผ ะฒ ะะตััะบะธะน ะผะธั ะธัะฟัะฐะฒะปััั ัะธััะฐัะธั!\n\n๐ ะ ะพัะฒะตั ะฝะฐะฟะธัะธ ะฝะฐะทะฒะฐะฝะธะต ะฝะพะฒะพะณะพ ัะตะทะพะฝะฝะพะณะพ ะฟัะพะดัะบัะฐ ะกะธะฝะฝะฐะฑะพะฝ ั ัะตัะฝะธะบะพะน",
    "answer": ["ะผะธะฝะธะฑะพะฝ"],
    "hint": "ะฆะะ, ะขะตะฐััะฐะปัะฝัะน ะฟัะพะตะทะด, 5ั1",
    "progress_bar": "๐ฟ---๐๏ธ--๐๏ธ--๐---๐๏ธ---๐๏ธ---๐ข----๐ฟ----๐ฐ----๐๏ธ---๐ [92%]"
  }
]
